GONÇALO FERREIRA

Birth Date

02/10/1993

Residenc

Matosinhos, Portugal

Phone

912631243

Email

goncalomb.pro@gmail.com



github.com/goncalomi



linkedin.com/in/goncalomi



goncalomi.github.io/portfolio

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Dart
- Python
- React
- Django
- Firebase
- Git e GitHub
- Material-UI
- Bootstrap

SOFT SKILLS

- Team Work
- High adaptability
- Responsible, Reliable
- Creative
- Determined
- Quick Learner

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English
- Spanish

Profile

Self-taught programmer, determined to evolve and driven by knowledge and new challenges.

I discovered my passion for programming eearly in 2020 when I tried to solve a problem in the company where I worked, which would be easily solved with technology. Since that moment, I have dedicated all my days to learning new technologies. After almost 1 year of constant learning, I had the opportunity to develop an Online Booking project for the company Fúria.

Eligible for an IEFP internship, I am looking for a job or internship opportunity.

Experiência



Porto, Portugal

Projecto - Freelancing Web Developer, 2021

- Built a Booking System using React and Typescript for the Front-End. Started developing the Back-End using Python with Django and built an API to serve data across all the platforms, switching to Firebase due to the simplicity. Also had to build a Back-office for Managing and Analytics with React and Typescript, Material-UI to speed up the design process and Chart.JS for the Dashboard.

FEELVIANA

Viana do Castelo, Portugal

Instructor de Wakeboard, 2014-2016

- Responsible for the Wakepark and Wakeboard Instructor in high season. Shop Assistant and responsible for the launching of FeelViana SportsCenter Online store during the low season.



Hahn, Germany Flight Attendat, 2017-2018



Porto, Portugal

Projects Manager and Wakeboard Instructor, 2016-2017 / 2018-2019 / Present



Porto, Portugal

Co-Owner and Bar Manager, 2014-2016

Educação

Externato Académico

Social-Economics Sciences 2011-2013